a wildlife viewing flash sharing app
I've always wanted to be James at all
and they read an article about making
friends with pros which I made you and
having an ability to share the data like
we're all Jane Goodall so like that I've
witnessed this squirrel behavior and
other people have and doing the things
that biologists would do like keeping
track of the population and being able
to identify because I have to say I
would not be able to identify crows
sorry bro I look the same to me I can't
tell if they're male or female how did
it go right there but I can't put an app
like a photo might be able to do that if
it's that easy I mean it's probably like
under them that you can tell the crow
apart but I think you actually probably
could tell individuals apart it may not
be able to do the gender but it would be
able to say that's hairy we create about
if we do that for humans we can do that
for any animal so being able to gather
data and share it so people who are
interested in that can do it of any age
and also contributes to the greater
knowledge of animals so a animal
behavior / ecological survey app that
helps us create community and gain
knowledge is Apple number ninety one
ninety six i feel like i just did 96 96
in case there's an extra one right